[This animation is recommended for audiences aged 18 and above]
[All the plots in this animation are fictional. Please do not imitate them in real life]
[Under 18s must be accompanied by an adult guardian]
[State S, Earth]
Time is running out.
Where is he?
I didn't see anyone. What's wrong?
He's gone. He's gone.
[Library]
They've come to find you.
Who are you?
Run.
Run all the way to the end of the corridor
and turn left.
And then?
The first door on your left hand.
Open the door.
I can't open it.
What should I do now?
Behind you.
[Unknown Call]
-Let's go watch a movie.
-Okay.
What's wrong with him?
Go!
Where is Shen Yao?
Seems
we don't have a choice now.
No.
You have no choice!
You'll pay a heavy price.
Nice imposing manner.
But...
This is really troublesome.
It's not easy to start a cycle.
What?
Stop joking!
You can't do anything here.
I hope this time
will have a different ending.
Shen Yao.
Xiaoxiu?
You're actually slacking off here.
I don't know how to solve a problem.
Can you help me with that?
Okay.
Let's go. Let me help you.
♫If I could escape from fate's predetermined path♫
♫And touch the true essence of time and space, the ultimate secret♫
♫Awakening this extraordinary destiny♫
♫Awakening another version of myself♫
♫The clearest, most resilient eyes of yours♫
♫Filled with the crystallization of infinite power♫
♫Releasing my true nature♫
♫Extracting every breath at lightning speed♫
♫Shinning Justice♫
♫The only truth in the duel♫
♫Now you guys are hearing my cry♫
♫My life was full of regrets♫
♫Restart♫
♫Striving, fighting, honing♫
♫Finding the future♫
♫Do not just dream it, have a try♫
♫Nothing can beat me, bravery's in my chest♫
♫I'll smash myself to protect your tenderness♫
♫I don't want to bow my head again♫
[Episode 1]
[Super Cube]
Cheers!
Oh no.
It's too hard.
I lost again.
Here's the punishment.
It's your turn to answer the question.
Shen Yao,
the truth for you
requires you to say the name of the person you're fond of.
Wang Xiaoxiu, why are you so excited?
Don't you really think that Shen Yao likes you?
No. No!
Although I've known Yao for a long time,
I don't think she has those affectionate feelings for me.
What am I talking about?
Yao? You're addressing her so intimately.
Rest assured.
Other girls won't like a guy of your type,
let alone Shen Yao.
All girls like a handsome boy like me.
Dream on!
You guys can just forget about it.
Only Prince Charming deserves Yao.
Right?
You can tell us secretly.
Do I have to?
Of course! You have to!
This is so embarrassing.
Since I was a kid,
I don't seem to have addressed her like that.
And you must be honest.
Then... The guy I like...
Is...
Wang... Wang Xiaoxiu.
Not me?
Are you kidding me?
It's ridiculous.
I'm not joking.
I've been paying attention to him
since elementary school.
Yao...
Yao actually confessed to me.
Turns out the taste of love...
[Dangerous action, please do not imitate]
Is pain.
You little rascal, how dare you take away the girl Big Brother likes!
Are you sick of living?
You're daydreaming about dating a girl far out of your league.
I'll throw you to feed the fish now!
-I don't know who spilled the beans
-You little rascal!
and got me caught by the hooligans of the North City Gang and made me questioned.
C-Calm down, bro.
We can talk.
Talk?
No chance in hell!
Why didn't you talk
before you took away Big Brother's girl?
This is Sun Jun.
He's an infamous hooligan
and Shen Yao's admirer.
No.
He's one of the harassers.
I think you're really gutsy to do that.
Cut the crap.
Throw him to feed the fish.
Yo, Yao,
long time no see.
Sun Jun?
Isn't this Xiaoxiu's number?
Where is he?
Yao, don't hang up.
I'll show you an interesting livestream.
Look, the pervert who keeps pestering you is right there.
Xiaoxiu?
Don't get Yao involved!
This is between us!
How dare you talk back?
Xiaoxiu!
Don't be so nervous.
I just want to talk to him.
Come on, Wang Xiaoxiu,
who do you think is qualified to be with Shen Yao?
Sun Jun, let him go!
Think carefully.
This is a matter of life and death.
You're smart. You must know the answer.
Sun Jun!
Sun Jun.
You can never be qualified to pursue Shen Yao.
You trash!
Xiaoxiu!
Does he really have a death wish?
And you. How could you drop him?
I... I didn't know he would hit me.
Wang Xiaoxiu! Wang Xiaoxiu!
Don't play dead. Come up to the surface quickly!
There's no response, Boss.
What should we do?
If I can't even protect my love,
it'll be meaningless for me to be alive.
The boy I'm into
is Wang Xiaoxiu.
I thought Wang Xiaoxiu was awesome.
Turns out he's a crybaby.
Yeah, look how fast he ran just now.
Xiaoxiu?
Shen Yao?
Didn't you bring an umbrella?
Let's go home together.
No.
Are you hiding here to avoid fulfilling your duties?
I can go home by myself.
[Experimental Elementary School]
But it's raining now.
[Dental Clinic]
It's okay. I can leave after the rain stops.
Xiaoxiu, your arm is bleeding.
Let me see.
No, no, no!
It might heal faster.
What's there to be shy about?
When did she become so gentle?
Shen Yao.
Thank you.
It stopped raining.
Let's go home together.
Seems there's light.
What's that?
Hot!
What's going on?
I think it has got inside my body!
What the heck?
This is...
I'm going to drown!
Am I dead?
Where am I?
Am I kidnapped by an alien?
Host,
you can draw a teleportation area
with a radius of 15 meters centered around me.
Then you can
teleport yourself to anywhere within the area.
What?
I'm going to fall to my death!
Find him!
They are actually looking for me.
Don't go home if you can't find him!
Did you hear anything?
Boss, were you hallucinating?
Cut the crap!
Hurry and find him!
Yes.
Weird.
I felt someone was in the sky.
Ouch. It hurts.
Why am I in the classroom now?
Did I teleport?
What happened?
Superpower?
Host,
you continuously activated space teleportation.
A voice is in my head?
Inside your body.
Inside my body?
Where? It's disgusting!
My phone.
So what are you?
Someone's here.
Who?
What's going on?
It's full of water.
Yao.
[Shen Yao]
Well...
You finally picked up!
Are you okay?
I thought you were dead.
Where are you?
I'm at home.
Why didn't you tell me you're home?
I was so worried.
I was so scared just now.
They went too far this time.
We should call the police.
No rush.
I'm quite smart.
I swam back while taking advantage of the chaos.
I guess they're still looking for me by the shore.
How can you still be laughing in this situation?
All right. It's getting late.
A lot has happened today.
You should rest early.
Wait!
No one will believe what happened today.
And I can't get Yao involved.
Host,
have you calmed down?
Why are you in my home?
I told you, I'm inside your body.
Again?
Welcome back.
It hurts.
Why am I in this space again?
And who is the Host?
I've established a stable connection with you physically.
So you're appointed as the user of the Horadric Cube,
the Ultimate Universe System.
In the words of you people from the Earth,
you are my master.
If you don't like the address,
I can also address you by other names.
Ultimate Universe System?
I've been sick of these silly words since elementary school.
What on earth is this place?
My appearance in the macroscopic physical world
is a cube with a volume of three cubic centimeters.
But inside is a three-cubic-centimeter portable space.
This place looks interesting.
So,
you made me teleport suddenly several times
tonight, didn't you?
Correct.
Cube, why did you help me?
To fulfill your wish
and become the king of the world.
By leveraging microwave radiation,
[Next Episode Preview]
you can see every object in the area.
Microwave radiation?
Where did you come from?
Is Wang Xiaoxiu here?
Oh no, Sun Jun's here.
Yao, don't be afraid.
You said you're a super system.
Who created you?
Master, nothing can be found.
You got away yesterday. You were just lucky.
I won't let you escape today.
Xiaoxiu, why did you hang up on me yesterday?
How can I make the superpower stronger?
The system has an upgraded function.
If you absorb Energy Gems,
your power will keep getting stronger.
♫Could it be that gravity also tilts toward you?♫
♫You start to shine brightly in the crowd♫
♫Why do I suddenly feel this way?♫
♫Why is it that whenever I need you most♫
♫You always appear♫
♫Can you sense all of my emotions?♫
♫Sharing every little thing, all day long♫
♫You've listened to all the songs I like♫
♫The story has reached this point, just one step away♫
♫Confessing♫
♫Can you say the words you've been meaning to say to me?♫
♫Let impulse bloom like cherry blossoms♫
♫My heart is floating♫
♫A little bit of confusion, sweet but helpless♫
♫A single gaze, and a happy surprise♫
♫Can you tell me the answer I'm looking forward to?♫
♫Looking at me, you're being naughty♫
♫Like a child♫
♫Another glance, and the starry sky lights up♫
♫Time slows down, but my heartbeat speeds up♫